

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

01116770689

jason\_aw1998@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jasonaw-han-wei

https://jasonaw.netlify.app/

https://github.com/jasonaw98

#### SOFT SKILLS

Leadership Determination

Communication Responsible

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

Software Development Life Cycle

Phyton Spring React Js

MySQL React Native Django

Flutter Java Hardhat

Solidity

#### AWARDS RECEIVED

Dean List Award Tri 1 19/20

MUET Achieved Band 4

# LANGUAGE

English (Advanced)

Mandarin (Intermediate)

Malay (Advanced)

# **JASON AW HAN WEI**

# WEB3 ENGINEER

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

2 years of experience in Software Development, gaining valuable transferable skills in relationship building, strategic planning and project management. Strong track record of quickly learning and adapting in new and complex situations. Eager to leverage a diverse range of talents in a new and engaging professional setting. Committed to lifelong learning and personal development.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Freelance Web3 Developer

- Build and deploy Full-Stack Dapps on Ethereum and Solana
- Experience in development tools such as Hardhat, Truffle, Anchor, React, Next.js
- Implement libraries such as OpenZeppelin and DappSys in smart contracts
- Knowledge of DeFi, Ethers.js, Web3js, Rust, Solidity, Solana SDK

# Software QA Engineer

Grass Valley | Mar 2021 - Present

- Prepare deployments with Kubernetes, Docker, Jenkins and applying CI/CD
- Conduct and write test cases for Web UI testing
- Conduct Automation test scenarios with Gatling,
   Scala and Selenium framework
- Perform impact analysis on new features, defect fixes and plan regression test suites.
- Conduct performance test with Jenkins, TestCafe,
   Protractor and Selenium
- Report and track defects using JIRA

#### **Software Engineer**

Software International | Nov 2020 - Feb2021

- React.js and Node.js for front-end development
- Spring and Java for back-end
- MySQL workbench for database
- Conduct project coordination, planning, and implementation of software development life cycle
- Create functional and technical application systems

# **PROJECTS**

#### Final Year Project

Malware Detection Using Radial Basis Function Neural Network | April 2019 - March 2020

- Building AI Prediction models in MATLAB
- Create GUI for presentation and interaction
- Process huge amounts of malware data
- Tweak to achieve the highest accuracy





https://jasonaw.netlify.app/



jason\_aw1998@hotmail.com



01116770689



www.linkedin.com/in/jason-aw-han-wei



https://github.com/jasonaw98

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Personal Portfolio

- Web Design
- React js and Gatsby
- Javascript and CSS

# Personal Project (Python)

- Web Automation
- Web development using Django
- Task Automation

# Freelance Project

- App Development using Flutter and React Native
- App Design with Adobe XD
- Web Automation using Selenuim
- Build responsive web apps with React Native

#### **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

# Multimedia University Bachelor of Information Technology (HONS) Security Tech | July 2017 - Oct 2020

- Major in Security Technology
- Dean list award Tri 1 19/20
- CGPA 3.33

# **Multimedia University**

Foundation in Life Science | April 2016 - 2017

#### CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

## Mobile Operation

MMU Orientation Committee | Mar 2018 - June 2018

- Prepare freshies for upcoming semester
- Guide freshies throughout the orientation

# **Club Assist Secretary**

MMU Masters Club (badminton) | April 2019 - Jun 2019

- Event planner
- Tournament handling

# Famine Group Leader

Famine 30 DIY Camp | April 2019 - Aug 2019

- Event Planner
- Assure safety of campers
- Leader of group

# Android Development

Thundercloud | April 2018 - Oct 2018

- Build GUI with Java and Kotlin
- App development with Android Studio